Okay, then, let's get to the big say, the big say.
The book and the intrigue of the book itself because of what you say.
Doesn't it make you want to buy it?
I mean, the font is a bit handwritten, but it's the same as any other book I've seen.
What should I do?
We're the kind of people who want something in return. We're the kind of people who want something in return.
We don't want unconditional love, we want it back.
Kettle and Idol
Well, here we are again today.
It's the kettle, the vacationers of Stardust.
Let's call today's guest. This is our idol.
Here they are. We, Se-no!
Super Strong Energy Positive Exciting Soul from Nagoya!
I'm Murasaki Purple Kakko kari, Yuzuki Oguro of Team Shachi.
Please give us your best regards.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much for coming. This is Oguro-san. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming.
Even Oguro-san, your own activities are amazing, aren't they?
No, no, no.
You know, Oguro-san, every Monday night at 9:00 p.m., you do a live broadcast,
It's a YouTube program.
You are well known for Yuzuki's Room.
Yuzuki's Room has the advantage that he does it every week no matter what,
It's amazing.
When I had a coronary, Rumpin and Chi-chan were there,
Rumpin and Chi-chan would put on my mask and come out as Yuzuki the Big Bath,
Afterwards, when the concert was over, I didn't have time to go back,
I would deliver the video in the dark from my car in the parking lot,
I would use my iPhone's lighting to deliver the video in the pitch dark of the car I was parked in,
It's been about 4 years now.
How many times have you done this?
Almost 200.
Two hundred.
That's amazing. You are like a senior to Yabana.
That's not true.
We usually call our fans "Tahmin,
When we are in Yuzuki's room, we become roommates with everyone who is watching us,
Is there a chemistry between your fans and Yuzuki's fans?
Yes, that's right. That's what they say.
What would you do if you were a senior?
What would you do if you were a senior member of YouTube?
It would be better to have a way to call your fans and listeners.
It would give me the ability to make quick decisions.
The fans'.
The ability to make quick decisions?
Isn't it the power to make decisions? Decisiveness. More like "quick thinking". It's not writing ability.
The ability to write.
The generation hasn't changed, has it? Mr. Omuro.
What should we make?
What would be good?
But since it's nighttime, maybe something with hot water.
Hot water?
No, but I would be very happy if you decide.
You don't mind if I decide?
Yes, you can. I'm fine with it. I can say that Omuro-san has already made the decision for me. Can I decide? No, it's fine.
I can say that Mr. Omuro has already made the decision.
Is that okay with you?
Yes.
Okay, then,
O-Yu.
Ooo-ooh.
O-Yoo.
Your yoo.
In your yoo.
O-Yoo.
I understand.
Yakan-kun's listener is O-Yoo from today.
Congratulations, Meimei Meimei. I see.
Were there other idols on the show that weren't staffers?
That's right. They appeared on the show a few times.
Do you negotiate with them yourself?
Sometimes they decide for me,
Basically, Yuzuki's Room is a place where you can make an appearance as long as you send me a message on line,
So I can answer right away.
I see.I see.
So, especially Ayami Kawase of Ukka,
I had a direct negotiation with her to be in the show on a regular basis,
She then communicates this to her manager, and the request is granted,
And then they tell the manager, and it happens quite often,
It is a band that is able to perform immediately.
Even though we have a relationship with them, I think this is something to look forward to every week.
What would Yagin-kun's room be like if he were to visit as a guest?
What kind of room would Yugi's room be like?
It would definitely be fun.
Really?
You can become a semi-regular guest in Yuguki's room once you appear.
What? Is it really that good? Tell me.
That's right. If Yakan-kun comes, you can become a semi-regular too.
I'm a semi-regular in Yuzuki's room?
Yes, I am. I can say that.
I can say I'm Yakan.
Yes, I can.
Isn't that great?
That's what I'm talking about.
I'll do my best when I have a kalea.
So, today's guest
Aubron Yukikan.
Thank you very much for having me.
I'm sorry, I couldn't ask you anything that I wanted to ask you.
You can't?
I can't.
I was really hoping to hear something that only I could get.
This program is for you, Nissy.
Yuzuki, Yuzuki Seisetsu-guy, Hina-chan...
Kotori
Pui-chan